麦琪∶本,到11点,
Maggie: OK Ben, we'll be back from the theatre by eleven,
我们会从剧院回来,除非你爸爸要宵夜..
unless your father springs an after show supper...we'll be back by eleven.
我们会在11点前回来的.你知道克莉丝的尿布在哪里,
Now, you know Chrissy's diapers are and I laid out her pajamas,
我已经把她的睡衣放好了,你最好不要叫任何朋友来家里玩.
and I don't think it's a very good idea for you to have any friends over.
臭虫∶嘿,本,大坏蛋妈妈今天要上电视!
Stinky: Hey Ben, Big Bad Mama's on cable tonight!
麦琪∶臭虫,我想你现在必须得回家了.
Maggie: Stinky, I think you're gonna have to go home now.
臭虫∶可是当我妈妈和爸爸租了录相带回来后,他们就不让我在家里.
Stinky: I'm not allowed at home whenever my mom and dad rent video tapes.
麦琪∶哈罗,迈克,有人打电话来谈你的车的广告!!
Maggie: Hello.Mike, somebody's calling about your car ad!!
本∶他不在这里;正在外面像一个成熟的人展示他的车呢.
Ben: He's not here; it's outside showing his car to a ripe one.
迈克∶我现在要卖不是像你所想的那种毛边的,
Mike: Now I'm not selling flash or chrome or any space-age ignition systems
铬合金或太空时代的点火系统的汽车.
like the cars you've been considering.
我讨论的是二次世界大战中一个国家的可靠的交通的主要参与者.我有提到,
I'm talking about reliable transportation from a country that was a major
它会飘行吗?
participant in world war two.Did I mention, it floats?
开萝尔∶迈克,很多东西都可以浮动.
Carol: Mike, a lot of things float.
迈克∶你伤害了我.
Mike: I am insulted.
开萝尔∶迈克..,忘掉吧.
Carol: Mike, forget it.
迈克∶开萝尔,这次就帮我一次,
Mike: No, no, Carol, do me just this one favour,
毕竟我们曾经也有过一段美好的时光.
after all the good times we've had together.
开萝尔∶我要算上这一次吗?
Carol: Do I count this one?
迈克∶还没有呢.开萝尔,只试试,我是说...
Mike: Not yet.Come on, just try me Carol, I mean look...
开萝尔∶住口,我会把它当作一次旋转.
Carol: Shut up, I'll take it for a spin
迈克∶对.
Mike: Good.Have a spin.
就是转转.对了,
By the way, you are sitting on something that did not require the slaughter
你现在正在坐的车决不会残杀一个有生命的东西.
of a single living thing.
开萝尔∶为什么会这么臭?
Carol: Then why does it smell in here?
迈克∶等卖出去后,我会告诉你的.
Mike: I'll tell you after the cheque clears.
开萝尔∶钥匙在哪里?
Carol: Where's the key?
迈克:有意思,开萝尔.我改进了一下那个不好使的钥匙.
Mike: Ah, interesting, Carol.I have done away with the inconvenience of keys.
开萝尔∶什么?
Carol: What?
迈克∶没错,只要把红线搭在蓝线上就可以起动了.
Mike: Yeah, you just touch the little red wire to the blue wire.
啊哈,我的防盗系统很有效吧.
Aha, I assume my anti-theft system is on guard.
麦琪:亲爱的,你为什么还要喝咖啡,我们要迟到了.
Maggie: Honey, why are you drinking coffee, we're gonna be late for the theatre.
杰森∶放松,麦琪,表演到8点45才开始呢.
Jason: Oh, relax Maggie, the curtain doesn't go up until eight forty five.
麦琪∶哦,百老汇戏剧好像很少在这个时间开始的.
Maggie: Oh, well that's an odd time for a Broadway play to start.
杰森∶他们必须清除掉所有的盘子.
Jason: Yeah, well they have to clear all the dishes.
麦琪∶什么盘子?
Maggie: What dishes?
杰森∶晚餐的盘子.
Jason: From the dinner.
麦琪∶杰森,什么百老汇戏院在表演前会提供晚餐?
Maggie: Jason, what Broadway theatre serves dinner before the show?
杰森∶哦,我说我们要去看百老汇戏剧,
Jason: Oh, I said we were going to a Broadway play,
但是我可没说要去百老汇戏院.
I didn't say were going to Broadway theatre.
麦琪∶那我们根本就不用去纽约了.
Maggie: So, we're not going into New York.
Jason: Not if you want to make it to Perambis by show time
麦琪∶那就是说,
Maggie: So, instead of going to Broadway,
我们根本就不是要去百老汇,而是要去新泽西州的一个戏剧餐馆,
we're going to a dinner theatre in New Jersey and we're not even having
并且我们还没有吃晚餐!
dinner!
杰森∶亲爱的,我不知道你是怎么想的,
Jason: Honey!I don't know about you,
但是,
but when I'm going to see Charles Nelson Riley,
当我要去看查尔斯纳尔逊瑞雷的时候,我不会去在乎他在哪里表演的.
I don't care where he performs.
麦琪:你好.我认为还是会打折的.
Maggie: Hello.Oh, yes I think it's still for sale.I'll try and find him.
我想办法找一下.迈克!
Mike!!!
迈克∶什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪∶你的电话,是要买车的.
Maggie: It's for you, it's about your car.
迈克∶哦,谢谢.
Mike: Oh, thanks.
杰森∶你要不要接听的?
Jason: Are you gonna talk?
迈克∶爸爸,如果我看上去很急切的想卖掉这辆车的话,
Mike: Err, yeah, Dad, come on,
那个家伙一定会觉得我的车有问题的.
if I look too anxious this guy's gonna think something's wrong with the car.
杰森∶我想确实有.
Jason: I thought there was.
迈克∶你好,先生.不好意思让你久等了,因为我正在向一个印刷经理在展示我的音响,她正在外面试驾呢.
Mike: See.Ah, hello, sir, sorry sorry for the wait, but I was just out
showing my V Dub to a young publishing executive who's test driving it now
杰森∶什么年轻的印刷经理?
Jason: What young publishing executive?
迈克∶是开萝尔!交易还没有最后确定下来呢,
Mike: Carol!Well the deal hasn't actually been finalized yet and frankly
坦白说,我不是太喜欢这个女人,
I don't even like the woman.Well you could...
你可以等到早上再来看,但是,我认为如果你在黄昏的时候能来看看的话..
you could wait till morning,
我是说,在卖掉以前.
but I think it would be better if you could see it when it's dark...
喂,喂.
I mean now...before it's sold.Hello.Hello.
杰森∶迈克,你为什么必须那么卑劣呢?
Jason: Mike, why do you have to be so sleazy?
迈克∶爸爸,我是在卖车.
Mike: Dad, I'm selling a car.Come on, what am I supposed to do?
难不成让我告诉他们,发动机是旧的,
I mean tell 'em that the engine's shot,
轮胎已经磨损了,刹车失灵了?
the tyres are balled and the breaks are bad?
杰森∶是的.
Jason: Yes.
迈克∶如果那样的话,我就赚不到钱了.
Mike: But then I'd only get what its worth.
杰森∶你知道吗,在一个父亲的一生中,有很多次当他深深的看着儿子的眼睛的时候,
Jason: You know there are times in a father's life when he looks into
他知道儿子做的很好.但是,这次不是这样.
his son's eyes and he knows he's done a good job.This isn't one of them.
开萝尔∶还有一股味道.他在追谁呀?
Carol: It's still here.Who's he after?Go around!Go around!
绕过去!绕过去!警官,
Officer, I didn't know you meant me.
我不知道你指的是我.我开车一直都很规矩的.
I've never been pulled over by a Police man before.
警察∶我拦你下来,是因为你车上的待售标记.
Policeman: I stopped you because of the For Sale sign.
开萝尔∶哦,你不会想要买这个垃圾吧.
Carol: Oh, you don't want to buy this piece of junk.
警察∶你是否介意把发动机关掉.
Policeman: Do you mind turning the engine off please.
开萝尔:你关吧,我不想动它.
Carol: Could you do it, I hate to touch bare wires.
你说这车是垃圾?
Is this car a piece of junk, or what?
警察∶我可以看看你的驾驶执照和注册证吗?
Policeman: May I see your operator's licence and registration please.
开萝尔∶为什么?
Carol: Why?
警察∶你正在驾驶一辆危险的车.
Policeman: You're operating an unsafe vehicle.
开萝尔∶恩,你其实不必告诉我那些.
Carol: Well, you didn't have to tell me that.
警察∶请出示你的驾驶执照和注册证!
Policeman: Your operator's licence and registration, please!
开萝尔:我敢肯定迈克已经毁掉了所有的罚单.
Carol: I bet Mike's registration is...
buried under all these unpaid parking tickets.
警察∶你说什么?
Policeman: Pardon me?
开萝尔∶一定有40或50份.
Carol: There must be forty or fifty in here.
警察∶小姐,恐怕你得换一种交通方式了.
Policeman: Miss, I'm afraid you'll have to arrange other transportation.
请下车.
Please step out of your vehicle.
开萝尔:这是我的车.
Carol: It's not my vehicle.
如果我有其他的,
If I had a vehicle, I would be happy to exit it.
我当然不用它.不过我能保证它不会发出像奶酪工厂一样的味道.
And I promise you my vehicle would not smell like a cheese factory.Excuse me.
不好意思.
Oops!
臭虫∶西维尔家,我是臭虫.
Stinky: Seaver residence, Stinky speaking.
开萝尔∶我要和迈克谈话.
Carol: I need to talk to Mike.
臭虫∶他不在.
Stinky: He's not here.
开萝尔∶那我的父母!
Carol: Then my parents!
臭虫∶他们出去看查尔斯曼森瑞雷了.
Stinky: They're out seeing Charles Manson Riley.
开萝尔∶那让本和我说话.
Carol: Then let me talk to Ben.
臭虫∶哦,开萝尔,怎么了?
Stinky: Oh, hi Carol, how's it going?
开萝尔∶快让本来接电话!!
Carol: Just get Ben!!
臭虫∶本,你的电话,开萝尔打来的!
Stinky: Ben, phone for you, it's Carol!
本∶留个口信,我在上大号呢.
Ben: Take a message, I'm in the can.
臭虫∶他在上大号.
Stinky: He's in the can.
开萝尔∶臭虫,我必须和他说,是生死攸关的情况.
Carol: Stinky, I need to talk to him, it's a life or death situation.
臭虫∶是生死攸关的情况!
Stinky: It's a life or death situation!
本∶我做的事情也是生死攸关的!
Ben: So's what I'm doing!
臭虫∶他正在做的事情也是生死攸关的.
Stinky: So is what he's doing.
开萝尔∶帮助本找到我的父母,告诉他们我...
Carol: Help Ben find my mom and dad and tell them that I'm...
臭虫∶开萝尔,你能不能等等,另外一个电话也响了...
Stinky: Errm, Carol, could you hold on, I think there's a call waiting.
开萝尔∶臭虫,我的事情要重要得多...
Carol: Look Stinky, this is more important...
臭虫∶哈罗,西维尔家,我是臭虫.哦,
Stinky: Hello, Seaver residence, Stinky speaking.Oh, hi Laura, it's Stinky.
你好劳拉,我是臭虫.本,劳拉林的电话.
Ben, it's Laura-Lynn!
本:好的,好的,
Ben: Alright, alright, alright!Hello.Oh, hi Laura.Aha.
好的!你好,劳拉林.
Both your parents are gone!Yeah, I think I could stop by some time tonight.
你爸妈都不在家!我想我今晚可以去.不过可能会晚一些.
I think it'll be late.Aha.Alright.Thanks.Bye.
好的,再见.
Well what are you waiting for Chrissy, grab Stinky and let's go.
臭虫∶我认为他有点反应迟钝的.本,
Stinky: I think he's got that backwards.Ben!
我再也不会接电话了,又不是找我的.
I'm not going to answer it, it's never for me.
电话录音.
Answer phone message
Maggie and Jason): It's OK, we know a lot of people try to leave cutesy
little messages on their machines, but not us.
Leave your massage at the tone, doo
da doo da.We'll call back when we're at home, do di doo da day
Hey
开萝尔∶(留口信在答录机上)臭虫,拿起电话!本你个该死的家伙,你跑哪里去了?一点都不好玩,我在监狱里,他们正打算帮我驱除虱子!最好有人能快点来保我出去.
Carol: (Leaving a message on the machine) Stinky, pick up!Ben you little rodent, where
are you?This isn't funny, I'm in jail and they're about to de-louse me
Somebody better do something quick
开萝尔∶我不属于监狱,我不应该和普通刑事犯,
Carol: I don't belong in here with common criminals...
小偷,败类,
thieves, degenerates, low-lifes...
低等人在一起..我相信你们也会和我有一样的感觉.
and I'm sure you cocktail waitresses feel the same way.
囚犯∶注意角落里的小坑.
Prisoner: Watch out for that little puddle in the corner.
开萝尔∶她还好吗?
Carol: Is she alright?
囚犯2∶你认为怎么样?
Prisoner 2: What do you think?
开萝尔∶保卫什么时候回来?
Carol: So, when does the guard get back?
囚犯∶11点半.
Prisoner: Eleven thirty.
开萝尔∶我不能等到那个时后,我要回家,我不属于这里的.
Carol: I can't wait till then.I have got to go home, I don't belong here.
囚犯∶哦,亲爱的,
Prisoner: Oh, darling, she melted my heart.
她熔化了我的新.你觉得我们让她出去,怎么样?
What the heck, what do you say we let her out?
开萝尔∶你能做到!
Carol: You can do that!
囚犯2:想想把.如果我能,我怎么还在这里?
Prisoner 2: Think about this.If we could do that, would we be here with you?
开萝尔∶我想你们肯定不能.
Carol: I guess then you probably can't.
囚犯∶你犯了什么事被抓进来的?
Prisoner: What did you do to get in here, anyway?
开萝尔∶什么也没有,绝对什么都没做!
Carol: Nothing, absolutely nothing!
囚犯2∶那他们以什么罪名起诉你?
Prisoner 2: What did they charge you with?
开萝尔∶你不会明白的,像我这样的人是不会被逮捕的.
Carol: You don't understand, people like me don't get arrested.
囚犯∶喔 !喔!
Prisoners: Oooh!Oooh!
开萝尔∶我在高中是全优学生.我爸爸是心理学家,
Carol: I got straight A's in high school.
我妈妈是记者.我在纽约5大区之一的曼哈顿上班.
My father is a psychiatrist, my mother is a journalist.
监狱不是为像我这样的人准备的,而是为...
I work in Manhattan, one of the five boroughs of New York.
我只能说..你们准备的!
Jail isn't for people like me, it's for people like...I'll just say it...you!
本∶好了,我和你做个交易,
Ben: OK, I'll make you a deal Chrissy;
克莉丝,如果你不说我们今天晚上去了哪里,我就再给你一个吸盒.
you don't breathe a word of where we were tonight you get another suck box.
克莉丝∶好.
Chrissy: OK.
麦琪∶杰森,我必须承认,
Maggie: Jason, I'll admit,
对查尔斯纳尔逊瑞雷能否演好奥赛罗,我还是有点不看好.
I had my doubts about Charles Nelson Riley doing Othello.
杰森∶嗨!.
Jason: Hey.
麦琪∶但是,我的天哪,他的确是有局限性!
Maggie: But, my gosh, the man has range.
克莉丝∶嗨.
Chrissy: Hi.
杰森和麦琪∶你好克莉丝.
Jason and Maggie: Hi Chrissy.
杰森∶克莉丝!
Jason: Chrissy!
麦琪∶克莉丝!你为什么会一个人在外面?
Maggie: Chrissy!What are you doing out here all alone?
杰森∶本,到底本回事?
Jason: Ben, what's going on here?
本∶哦,我只是想拿一个吸盒给她.
Ben: Oh, I was just gonna give her this suck box.
杰森∶你叫我什么?
Jason: What did you call me?
本∶你解释,妈妈.
Ben: You explain it, Mom.
麦琪∶不本,还是你解释看,
Maggie: No Ben, you explain why you and your baby sister are up past midnight
为什么你和妹妹深更半夜的还没有睡觉,为什么她现在还穿着这件茄克.
and why she is wearing this jacket.
本∶嘿,她正在要脱掉外套呢.
Ben: Hey, she's going through this overcoat stage.
我整个晚上一直都和她呆在长沙发椅上.
I've been with her, on the couch, all evening.
杰森∶这就是为什么会有电话留言的原因?
Jason: Is that why there are phone messages?
本∶你们不是告诉过我,当我一个人单独在家的时候,让我不要接电话吗?
Ben: Ah, well you know what you've told me about not answering the phone when I'm home alone.
麦琪∶本,我们从来都没有这样跟你说过.
Maggie: Ben, we never told you any thing like that.
本∶哦,对,那是布什总统说的.
Ben: Oh, right that was President Bush.
麦琪∶那这么说当这些信息进来的时候,你都已经听过了.
Maggie: So you've heard all these phone messages as they were coming in.
开萝尔∶(留口信在答录机上)臭虫,拿起电话!本你个该死的家伙,你跑哪里去了?一点都不好玩,我在监狱里,他们正打算帮我驱除虱子!最好有人能快点来保我出去.
Answer phone Messages: (Carol) Stinky, pick up!Ben, you little rodent, where are you?This isn't funny.I'm in jail and they're about to de-louse me.Somebody better do something quick!
杰森∶监狱!
Jason: Jail!
答录机留言还在继续∶有人在家吗?妈妈!妈妈!
Answer phone message continued: Is anybody there?Mom!Mom!
麦琪∶哦,是的宝贝儿,我来了!!哦,快点,杰森.
Maggie: Oh, yes honey, I'm coming!!Oh, come on, Jason.
答录机信息∶(劳拉林)你好本杰明,这是劳拉林,我今晚过的很开心.等下次我父母不在家的时候,我们再做一次.
Answer phone message: (Laura-Lynn) Hi Benjamin, this is Laura-Lynn, I had a great
time tonight.Let's do it again next time my parents are out
麦琪∶本,这是很严重的.
Maggie: Ben, this is serious.
本∶你跟我说吗?城里肯定有些孩子冒充我,
Ben: You're telling me.
跑去和我女朋友一起!
There's some kid going around this town pretending he's me, with my girl!
典狱官∶西维尔!开萝尔西维尔!
Prison Warden: Seaver!Carol Seaver!
开萝尔∶是.
Carol: Yes.
典狱官∶西维尔小姐,代表纽约州向你说对不起.像你这么好的人是不应该在监狱里的.
Prison Warden: Miss Seaver, on behalf of the state of New York, we're sorry.A fine person like you doesn't deserve to be in jail.
开萝尔∶只是时间的问题.大家,大家!我们的典狱官有话要说!
Carol: Well, it's about time.Everybody, everybody!Our cell mother has an announcement to make.
典狱官∶我开玩笑的,蠢人.
Prison Warden: I'm kidding twerp.
你的父母来保释你出狱了.
You're parents are here to bail your uptown butt out of here.
杰森∶我明天当然需要你出庭了,锡德,你是我的律师.
Jason: Of course I want you in court tomorrow, Sid, you're my lawyer.
你能不能先别管那些乱七八糟的事情了,好,
Well could you possible move the racket ball thing?
好,我们跟法官见面的时间是8点,据说起诉理由是拘捕.
Yeah, yeah, our time to see the judge is eight a.
不,不,不是迈克,
m, to tell us the charge is resisting arrest.
是开萝尔.好,
No, no, it's not Mike, it's Carol.Alright.Goodbye.
再见.一切都准备就绪,沸曼会在那里.
It's all set, Fiman will be there.
麦琪∶哦,杰森,开萝尔在这个可怕的地方呆了整个晚上.
Maggie: Oh, Jason, Carol's been in this horrible place all evening.
杰森∶;亲爱的,一切都准备好了,他们说她也很好.
Jason: Honey, it's alright, they said she's OK.
麦琪∶哦,
Maggie: Oh, Jason honey,
杰森,
I'm stared to even think of what went on here tonight with our poor baby.
我根本不敢想像今天晚上发生在我们可怜的宝贝身上的一切.你知道她是那么的脆弱.
You know how fragile she is.
我们必须设法抚平她所受到的惊吓.
We're just gonna have to try to put our frightened little girl back together.
开萝尔∶你们该死的去了哪里?
Carol: Where the hell have you been?
杰森:嗨……
Jason: Hey...
开萝尔∶我被关在监狱里面6个小时,有一个强壮的女人对我胡说八道.
Carol: I have been in jail for six hours and a very large woman drooled
而妓女们都嘲笑我.
on me.Prostitutes laughed at me!
杰森∶哦,宝贝,我们一直在那里.不是那里!
Jason: Oh, honey, we've all been there.Not there!Not there, exactly...
不是那里,会很靠近..说昏话的强壮女人!
but near...close...Drooling...a large woman!
开萝尔∶我不能等到去法院见那个警察了.
Carol: I can't wait to get that police man in court.
杰森∶说到法院,开萝尔.
Jason: Well, speaking of court, Carol.
开萝尔∶对,我们什么时候跟律师见面.
Carol: Alright, now when do we meet with the lawyer.
麦琪∶明天,我们见法官前就会见到律师.
Maggie: Tomorrow, right before we see the judge.
开萝尔∶但是我们需要时间去收集证据,会见证人,拿笔录供词...
Carol: But we need time to gather our evidence, interview witnesses, take depositions
杰森∶等等!不用这些.
Jason: Hey, w...w...ait...wait, wait!It's gonna be a lot simpler than that.
开萝尔∶真的?
Carol: Really?
杰森∶是的,沸曼说只要你明天在法官的小室里认了罪,
Jason: Yes, Fiman says as long as you plead guilty in the judge's chambers
就不会有审讯,没有听证,你的纪录上什么都不会有.
tomorrow, there'll be no trial, no hearing, nothing goes on your record.
开萝尔∶但是我是无罪的!
Carol: But I'm not guilty!
麦琪∶宝贝儿,
Maggie: Honey, that's not the important thing here!
那都不重要了!
What's important is that you don't get yourself in deeper than you already
重要的是你不要把自己陷的太深了!
are.
开萝尔∶有什么比公正更重要?
Carol: What's more important than justice?
迈克∶我的该死的车在哪里?
Mike: My car, where the heck is it?
开萝尔∶被扣押了,和我一样,扣押了6个小时.
Carol: Impounded, like I was for six hours.
迈克∶太可怕了.
Mike: Oh, that's horrible.
开萝尔∶恩,曾经是的,迈克,但是,现在我好很多了.
Carol: Well, it was for a while, Mike, but I'm OK now.
迈克∶他们扣押了我可爱的小车.
Mike: They got my cute little car.
麦琪∶迈克,你的姐姐在今晚经历了那么多,你能不能表示一点点的同情.
Maggie: Mike, your sister has been through a lot tonight, can you please show a little compassion.
迈克∶对监狱里的事情我深感同情.但是,我怎么样才能拿回我的车呢?
Mike: Oh, sorry about the jail thing.How am I gonna get my car back!?
开萝尔∶迈克,不要再提你的车了!我的问题要比该死的车大!
Carol: Mike, forget your car!This is bigger than your stinking car!
迈克∶天拉,监狱让你变成了一个怀恨的女人.
Mike: Boy, prison has made you a bitter woman.
开萝尔∶妈妈,爸爸,
Carol: Mom, Dad, I want a full vindication,
我想要一个完整的辩护,我决不会停止,直到我的罪名被洗清.
and I will not rest until my name is clear.
杰森∶等等,开萝尔,
Jason: W...wait, wait, Carol, this could drag on for months and months.
如果那样的话,可能会拖好几个月.你真的想要这样吗?
Do you really want that to happen?
开萝尔∶你总是告诫我,让我不要说谎,
Carol: Well you always told me not to lie,
所以当我是无辜的时候,我决不会说自己有罪.
and I do not want to say I'm guilty when I'm not.
麦琪∶如果到了审讯后,他们证明你真的是犯了拒捕罪的话,
Maggie: What if this thing goes to trial and somehow they find you guilty
你会被判刑的.
of resisting arrest.You could go to prison.
开萝尔∶我是无辜的.
Carol: I'm innocent.
麦琪∶开萝尔,有时他们会判无罪的人有罪的,
Maggie: Carol, sometimes they find innocent people guilty,
你必须记得什么才是最重要的.
you've got to remember what's important here.
迈克∶我的车!
Mike: My car!
麦琪∶不,是你的将来.
Maggie: No.Your future.
开萝尔:妈妈!
Carol: Mom!
杰森∶开萝尔,开萝尔,听着,
Jason: Carol, Carol, listen, I know more about this thing than you do, OK.
我懂的比你多.所以我现在告诉你,
And I'm telling you, you're gonna go down the judges chamber,
你要到法官的房间去认罪,就这样!没有了!
you're gonna plead guilty, that's it!Period!
开萝尔∶我以为我已经出了监狱了.
Carol: But...And I thought I was out of jail.
杰森:迈克!明天上午七点半,我们准时去法庭,好么?
Jason: And Mike, you!Seven thirty sharp tomorrow, we leave for the court, OK?
迈克∶我,我去能干什么?
Mike: Me, what do you want me for?
杰森∶法官要求你的出席..
Jason: The judge requested your presence...
关于一工具箱的没有付的违规停车罚单.
something about a glove compartment full of unpaid parking tickets.
迈克∶幸好他没检查后备箱.
Mike: Well, good thing he didn't check the trunk.
麦琪∶亲爱的,差不多要到时间了,我们的律师呢?
Maggie: Honey, it's almost time.Where's our lawyer?
杰森∶不必担心,麦琪,锡德从来没有让我失望过.
Jason: Don't worry, Maggie; Sid has never let me down.
迈克∶嘿,我想事情还不会太坏,我有个感觉,觉得这个法官应该会是个很不错的人.
Mike: Hey, this isn't gonna be so bad, I have a feeling this judge is gonna be pretty cool.
开萝尔∶为什么?
Carol: Why?
迈克∶你看,上面写着.赫尔曼法官.你想想有多少这样的花花公子会让你称呼他们的名字?
Mike: It says, Judge Hermann.I mean how many of these dudes would want you
to call them by their first names
西德尼∶杰森,对不起,我来迟了!
Sidney: Jason, sorry I'm late!
杰森∶哦,锡德,没关系.我很高兴你能赶到.
Jason: Oh, Sid, it's alright.I'm glad you made it.
麦琪∶这么说这就是锡德了.
Maggie: So this is Sid.
西德尼∶实际上是西德尼,你一定是麦琪.
Sidney: Sidney actually.You must be Maggie.
麦琪∶噢呼.
Maggie: Uh hu.
西德尼∶你知道,我不知道为什么我们以前没有见过面.
Sidney: You know, I don't know why we haven't met before.
迈克∶我知道.
Mike: I do.
杰森∶麦琪,别再想她看起来像什么了.西德尼是一个很合格的律师.
Jason: Maggie, forget what she looks like.Sidney is a qualified attorney.
西德尼∶哇,这就是法官房间.
Sidney: Wow, so this is what a judges chambers looks like.
杰森∶你知道很多律师实际上都不用在法院房间工作的.她通过了律师职业资格考试,
Jason: You know a lot of lawyers don't actually work in the court room.
麦琪.
She passed the bar, Maggie.
麦琪∶没有人主动去给她买杯饮料吗?
Maggie: Why, nobody offered to buy her a drinky?
西德尼∶你是开萝尔,对吗?
Sidney: You're Carol, right?
开萝尔∶恩.
Carol: Mmm.
西德尼∶不必担心,我会照顾好你的.
Sidney: Don't worry, I'll take good care of you.
迈克∶我是迈克.我会小心照顾我自己的.
Mike: I'm Mike and I could use a little care myself.
西德尼∶为了救你的姐姐,我可能会把你抛给那些贪婪成性的人.
Sidney: I may have to throw you to the wolves to save your sister.
麦琪∶这就是你为什么不介意带我们的律师出去吃午餐,
Maggie: So, this is why you didn't mind taking our lawyer out to lunch
并且不介意付钱的原因.
and didn't mind paying.
法官∶旧法官的玩笑.
Judge: Old judge's joke.
西德尼∶法官阁下,我的委托人...
Sidney: Your honour, my client...
法官∶宝贝,
Judge: Hold your water a sec, honey.
先喝点水.
Now, this is the case of the people versus the rude little college girl,
这就是警察告粗鲁而矮小的女大学生的案子?
right?
开萝尔∶其实直到下个秋季,我才去哥伦比亚上学.
Carol: Well, I don't really start Columbia till next fall.
西德尼∶开萝尔,法官不想听你的大学计划.
Sidney: Carol, the judge doesn't want to hear about your college plans.
法官∶愿意听.你主修什么?
Judge: Sure he does.What are you majoring in?
开萝尔∶我现在还没有完全肯定.我曾经想过要去学点商务方面的东西,
Carol: Well, I'm not really sure yet.
但是最近我...
I was thinking of something in business, but lately I've...
西德尼:尊敬的法官,请允许我的当事人陈述.
Sidney: Your honour, if we may my client would like to enter her plea now.
法官∶别急,律师.你的行为让人觉得你好像要迟到什么非法的勾当了.
Judge: Easy councilor, you act like you're late for a racket ball game,
恩,你的衣服很好看.
or something.Mmm, that's a nice dress.
这里写着,你要认拒捕罪,然后接受罚金.
Now, it says here, you're gonna plead guilty to resisting and pay a fine.
开萝尔∶我...
Carol: Well...
西德尼∶先生,是这样的.
Sidney: That's correct sir.
开萝尔∶是的.
Carol: That's correct.
法官∶啊哈.你发誓.
Judge: Aha.You swear.
麦琪∶几乎从不.
Maggie: Hardly ever.
开萝尔∶法官大人,我还有话要说.
Carol: Your honour, there is something I'd like to say.
法官∶叫我赫尔曼.
Judge: Call me Herman.
开萝尔∶赫尔曼法官.
Carol: Just Herman.
法官∶行,为什么不行?那是我的名字.你是谁?
Judge: Sure, why not?It's my first name.Who the hell are you, sport?
迈克∶我是...你知道,她的弟弟.
Mike: I'm...you know, her brother.
法官∶哦,违规停车罚单孩子.晚点我在找你.
Judge: Oh, the parking ticket kid.I'll deal with you later.
迈克∶谢谢,法官大人.
Mike: Thank you, your holiness.
开萝尔∶法官...
Carol: Look, judge...
法官∶赫尔曼.
Judge: Herman.
开萝尔∶赫尔曼,我认为我没有做错事情.
Carol: Herman, I don't think I did any thing wrong.
杰森∶开萝尔.
Jason: Carol.
法官∶你是她的辩护人?
Judge: Are you her defendant?
杰森:不是.
Jason: No.
法官∶你想要做吗?
Judge: You wanna be?
杰森∶不,先生.
Jason: No, sir
法官∶那就坐下.开萝尔,你想怎么样来处理这件事情?
Judge: Then, sit.Now, Carol, how do you wanna handle this thing?
开萝尔∶我有什么选择?
Carol: Well, what are my choices?
法官∶比如说正如堪萨斯小姐这里所解释的一样,
Judge: Well, as Miss Kansas here's probably explained,
你可以认罪,
you can plead guilty and pay a fine,
然后交罚金;你也可以起诉,
or you can go to court and maybe pay a bigger fine,
可能会需要付更多的罚金或被判一段时间的刑.
or maybe get a jail term.
开萝尔∶那我能不能在认罪的时候做一个解释?
Carol: Well, could I plead guilty with an explanation?
法官∶解释什么?
Judge: What's the explanation?
开萝尔∶解释我是无罪的.
Carol: That I'm not guilty.
评断∶对不起,这样是行不通的.
Judge: Sorry, it doesn't work that way.
开萝尔∶我当时只是想设法向警察解释我的情况,但是当车门碰撞到他的腹股沟时候,他以为我要逃跑,所以就把我逮捕了.
Carol: You see, I was just trying to explain my situation to that policeman, but he took it the wrong way when the door hit him in the groin and arrested me.
杰森∶开萝尔...你妈妈有一些事情要说.
Jason: Carol...your mother has something to say.
法官∶不,她不能说话.
Judge: No, she doesn't.
开萝尔∶我知道我的父母和其他所有人都想要我认罪,但是,
Carol: And I know my parents and everybody else wants me to say I'm guilty,
我明明知道自己没罪怎么可以去认罪呢?
but how can I when I know I'm not?
法官:因此,你希望纽约政府花费几千块钱和大量的时间来对你的案子进行调查,
Judge: So, you want the state of New York to spend thousands of Dollars
而不管是时间还是金钱,
and hours of work,
你根本都耗不起的情况下,只为了证明你是无辜的.
and none of which it can afford so that you can plead not guilty.
开萝尔∶是的,先生,我就是这样想的.
Carol: Yes, sir, I do.
法官∶恩,我也是这样认为你的.本案撤诉.
Judge: Well, that's how I find you.Case dismissed.
杰森,锡德和麦琪∶什么?
Jason, Sid and Maggie: What?
法官:技术上来讲,你的行为构成了拒捕.但是我认为我们的国家还要生存下去;我知道有很多无罪的人,因为怕麻烦,而不去证明自己的无辜,就直接认罪了.
Judge: Oh, I think you probably did resist arrest, technically.
我也知道我们的法律体系确实还不够完善,但是我愿意回报那些利用法律的优点取代害怕其缺点的人.哦对了,如果你还没有确定专业的话,秋季开学的时候,也许你可以尝试着成为我们中的一员.这样会是一个不错的计划.
But I think the republic
will survive; see I got a problem with people who plead guilty when they're
not
just because doing the right thing is too much of a hassle.Now, I know
that our system of law around here isn't perfect,
but I like rewarding people who
count its virtues instead of being afraid of its flaws.And by the way, if
you're still looking for something to major in, in the fall,
you might try bringing
some of that hutzbah of yours into my line of work.Good dental plan
开萝尔∶谢谢法官大人.非常感谢.
Carol: Thanks your honour, thanks very much.
迈克∶走了,开萝尔!
Mike: Way to go, Carol!
法官∶哦,我几乎忘记了违规停车罚单.
Judge: Oh, I almost forgot about that parking ticket thing.
杰森∶哦...
Jason: Oh, errm...
法官∶西维尔先生,据说在你的工具箱里有价值400美元的罚单.
Judge: Mr.Seaver, it says you had four hundred Dollars worth of tickets in your glove compartment.
迈克∶是的,法官大人.
Mike: Ah, yes, your grace.
法官∶顶端还有一个活动的大众汽车抹布,对吗?
Judge: This is a VW rag top convertible isn't it?
迈克∶是,但是...
Mike: Well yeah, but what does that...
法官∶正好我一直在替我的没用的外孙在找这个呢,
Judge: It so happens that I've been looking for one of those for my no
我用400美金跟你买.
account grandkid.I'll give you four hundred Dollars for it.
迈克∶400美金,它最少值...
Mike: Four hundred Dollars, well it's worth at least...
法官∶西维尔先生,我们检查了后备箱.
Judge: We looked in the trunk, Mr.Seaver.
迈克∶卖了.快乐的汽车.
Mike: Sold.Happy motoring.
法官∶明智的决定!
Judge: Good decision!Good decision!
明智的决定!
Now if you folks will excuse me,
好,我要失陪一下,
I got to get back into the court room and send some bad guys to the
回去把那些有罪的坏蛋都送进监狱.
cooler...just the guilty ones.
麦琪∶宝贝儿,我是如此的为你感到骄傲.
Maggie: Honey, I'm so proud of you.
杰森∶嗨!你真的是个人才!
Jason: Hey, you were really something.
西德尼∶我做的还好.
Sidney: I did alright.
迈克:看来这些天看法律没有白看啊.
Mike: Hey, all those weeks of watching LA Law really paid off, huh?
开萝尔∶爸爸,我只是不能认罪.
Carol: Dad, I just couldn't.
杰森∶开萝尔,是我该向你道歉.
Jason: Hey.Carol, it's me who owes you an apology.
幸亏你有胆敢违背我的意思.
Thank God you had the good sense to disobey me.
开萝尔∶你说什么?
Carol: Pardon me?
麦琪∶开萝尔,你爸爸的意思是说有的时候,
Maggie: Carol, I think what your father's means is that sometimes it's
最好可以忽略他.
just best to...ignore him.
杰森∶比如说像这样的事情.
Jason: Something like that.
开萝尔∶谢谢.我必须到办公室去了.
Carol: Thank you.Now I've got to get to the office.
杰森∶好了,我们送你去.
Jason: Come on, we'll give you a lift.
开萝尔∶哦,我们能不能中途在哥伦比亚大学停一下?
Carol: Oh, on the way, can we stop at Columbia University?
杰森∶可以,为什么呢?
Jason: Sure, why?
开萝尔∶我想去拿一份目录.
Carol: I wanna pick up a catalogue.
麦琪∶我们不是有目录吗?
Maggie: Don't we have other catalogues?
开萝尔∶没有基本法律.
Carol: Not the pre-law one.
杰森∶法律?开萝尔,你要...
Jason: Law?Carol, are you...
开萝尔:爸爸,
Carol: Dad, I'm just thinking.
我正想呢.昨天晚上我突然意识到这种事情总是会遇到,
Now, it didn't occur to me till last night that something like this could
别人也会遇到.
happen to me, and if it can it can happen to anybody.
杰森∶法律学校!
Jason: Law school!
麦琪∶好哦!宝贝儿.
Maggie: Alright!Oh honey.
杰森∶如果开萝尔变成了一个律师,我们就不再需要锡德了.
麦琪∶亲爱的,我们已经不再需要她了.
00:22:24,700
Jason: If Carol becomes a lawyer, we won't need Sid anymore. Maggie: Honey, we don't need Sid anymore now.